continuum.io 2016-03-24

# Privacy Policy | Continuum

Continuum Analytics, Inc. (“Continuum, “we” or “us”) offers products and services to site visitors customers. This privacy policy (“Policy”) describes how we gather and use personal information and other information collected by us in connection with our business. We take reasonable steps to protect such information and your privacy consistent with the guidelines set forth in this policy and with applicable United States and international laws.

In this policy, “user” or “you” means any person

(i) registering with us by creating an account,

(ii) using or otherwise benefiting from the Service, or

(iii) participating in any other activities available through the Service.

By accessing or using our websites, products and services, you acknowledge that you have read, understand, and agree to be bound  by this policy and our service terms and conditions. If you do not agree to these terms, do not use the websites, products or services.

Continuum Analytics, Inc. (“Continuum”) operates several websites, including continuum.io, anaconda.org, wakari.io and pydata.org.

### Information we collect

**Personal Information:** We collect Personal Information you disclose when you register and/or pay for a product or service, including your first and last name, home address, billing address, telephone number, email address, and information regarding your method of payment. When you access our websites or servers, we automatically recognize your Internet Protocol (“IP”) address.

**Aggregate Information:** We collect various types of statistical user information to create aggregated data to analyze and improve our products and services. This aggregated data does not contain any Personal Information.

**Tracking Information:** We, and our third-party service providers, may use general browser tracking technologies such as cookies and web beacons in order to operate efficiently and to collect data related to usage and marketing of our products and services. Tracking Information may include, without limitation, the type of browser you are using, your IP address, what pages you visit, what links you clicked on, and whether you opened text message or email communications we send to you.

We may also use web tracking technologies on our products and services, or in email communications, to collect information about actions that users take when they interact with us, and our third-party vendors may also do so. We do not correlate tracking information to individual user Personal Information; however, some tracking information may include data unique to you, such as IP address data. You may be able to modify your browser settings to alter which web tracking technologies are permitted when you use the service, but this may affect the performance of the service.

### How we use the information we collect

**Personal Information:** We use and store Personal Information only for the purposes of collecting payment, delivering products and services to you, to enhance and analyze the operation of the service, and for the internal operational and administrative purposes of the service.

We use Personal Information for internal and service-related purposes only. Continuum does not rent, sell, or share Personal Information about you with other people or unaffiliated companies, except (a) to provide products or services you've requested, (b) when we have your permission, or when working with Contractors operating under confidentiality agreements and bound by this Privacy Policy. to help us communicate with you about offers from Continuum.

Continuum may disclose Personal Information in cooperation with law enforcement agency requests, court orders or subpoenas, or if deem it necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our Terms of Service or End User License Agreements (EULA), to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing our products and applicable laws, or as otherwise required or permitted by law or consistent with legal requirements.

We may transfer Personal Information about you if we or one of our business units are acquired by or merged with another company.

**Aggregate information:** We use aggregated data to understand our customers, and to enhance the service.

**Tracking information:** We use Tracking Information to administer our products and services, to understand how well our products and services are working, to store your user preferences and customize your experience, and in some cases, to develop aggregate, statistical usage information. This allows us to determine which features customers like best, and to measure overall effectiveness of and improve our products and services.

**Legal exception:** Notwithstanding the above, we may use Personal Information and other information we collect to the extent required by law or legal process, to resolve disputes, to enforce our agreements with you (including this Policy and the terms and conditions of the service), or to protect our legal rights or the rights of third parties.

**Email communications:** If you create an account and provide your email address, we may send you administrative and promotional emails. If you wish to opt out of promotional emails, you may do so by following the unsubscribe instructions in the email. All users receive administrative emails, and you cannot opt out of them while you remain an account holder.

### Information we disclose to third parties

**Personal Information:** We will not disclose your Personal Information to any third parties except:

(i) to third-party contractors engaged to provide services on our behalf (our “Contractors”), such as hosting and communications services, analyzing data and usage of our products and services, operating our products and services, providing support and maintenance services for our products and services, or providing customer support. We enter into agreements with all Contractors that require Contractors to use the Personal Information they receive only to perform services for us, and

(ii) when we have your consent.

**Aggregate information:** We may disclose anonymous, aggregated information to third parties such as potential business partners, advertisers, and funding sources, in order to describe our business and operations.

**Tracking information:** We disclose tracking information to third-party advertisers, advertising agencies, and contractors, in order for us and such third parties to analyze the performance of our products and services and the behavior of users, to operate and improve the service, and to target advertising to users. We may also publish this information in order to promote our products and services.

Network operators: Use of our products and services may involve use of the services of third-party telecommunications carriers. Such carriers are not our Contractors, and any information that a carrier collects in connection with your use of our products and services is not Personal Information for purposes of this Policy and is not subject to this Policy. We are not responsible for the acts or omissions of such telecommunications carriers.

### Privacy settings/opt out

If you would like your Personal Information permanently removed from our database, please contact us at support@continuum.io; we will promptly delete your account and you will no longer receive communications from us. Your removal from the mailing list or database will not remove records of past transactions or delete information stored in our data backups and archives. Data on past transactions and data stored in backups and archives will be maintained and/or deleted in the ordinary course of our business.

### Access and updating your information

To review or amend your email address or contact details held in our database., please adjust your account settings or email [support@continuumm.io](mailto:support@continuum.io?subject=Privacy%20Policy%20Inquiry%20from%20Website).

### Security and external links

We use reasonable security precautions to protect the security and integrity of your Personal Information in accordance with this Policy and applicable law. However, because no Internet or mobile transmission is completely secure, we cannot guarantee that security breaches will not occur. Without limitation of the foregoing, we are not responsible for the actions of hackers and other unauthorized third parties that breach our security procedures.

The Service may contain links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of those sites. Users should be aware of this when they leave our Service and review the privacy statements of each third-party website. This Policy applies solely to information collected by the Service.

### Online Forums

Continuum provides online forums where users may post information and exchange ideas. Be careful not to disclose any Personal Information as part of any posts, even if requested to do so by other posters. Continuum will not be responsible in the event that you disclose Personal Information during any communication with other site users. You acknowledge and agree that content provided by others may include content owned by independent content providers (including other users). Continuum does not guarantee  accuracy, completeness or usefulness of any forum content. We do not review forum content before it is posted, but we reserve the right to remove any forum content at any time that we deem it to be harmful, offensive, or otherwise in violation of this Agreement.

### California Users’ Privacy Rights

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits California residents to request and obtain from us once a year, free of charge, information about the personal information we disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year, if any. If applicable, this information would include a list of the categories of personal information that was shared and the names and addresses of all third parties with which we shared information in the preceding calendar year. If you do not want your name and contact information to be shared with any company or organization, you may notify us at any time by emailing support@continuum.io or by mail.

### Users from outside the U.S.

Continuum and our servers are located in the United States and are subject to applicable state and U.S. laws. If you choose to access or use the Service, you consent to the use and disclosure of information in accordance with this Policy and are subject to such laws.

With respect to personal data relating to residents of the European Economic Area (EEA), Continuum adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles. Our Safe Harbor Certification with the U.S. Department of Commerce covers customer relationship data and human resources data, as further explained in the Continuum EEA Safe Harbor Notice.

### Amendments to this Privacy Policy

We may modify or amend this Policy from time to time. If we make any material changes, as determined in our sole discretion, in the way in which Personal Information is collected, used, or transferred, we will notify you of these changes by modification of this Policy by updating this Privacy Policy on our website. Your continued use of the websites, products and services constitutes acceptance of the terms of this Privacy Policy.

Notwithstanding any modifications we may make, any Personal Information collected by us from you will be treated in accordance with the Policy as it was in effect at the time the information was collected, unless we obtain your consent.
